<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.chylex.intellij.inspectionlens</id>
  <name>Inspection Lens</name>
  <vendor url="https://chylex.com">chylex</vendor>
  
  <description><![CDATA[
    Shows errors, warnings, and other inspection highlights inline.
    <br><br>
    Simply install the plugin and inspection descriptions will appear on the right side of the lines.
    Shown inspection severities are <b>Errors</b>, <b>Warnings</b>, <b>Weak Warnings</b>, <b>Server Problems</b>, <b>Typos</b>, and other inspections from plugins or future IntelliJ versions that have a high enough severity level.
    Each severity has a different color, with support for both light and dark themes.
    <br><br>
    The plugin is not customizable outside of the ability to disable/enable the plugin without restarting the IDE.
    If the defaults don't work for you, I would recommend either trying the <a href="https://plugins.jetbrains.com/plugin/17302-inlineerror">Inline Error</a> plugin which can be customized, or proposing your change in the <a href="https://github.com/chylex/IntelliJ-Inspection-Lens/issues">issue tracker</a>.
    <br><br>
    Inspired by <a href="https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=usernamehw.errorlens">Error Lens</a> for VS Code, and <a href="https://plugins.jetbrains.com/plugin/17302-inlineerror">Inline Error</a> for IntelliJ Platform.
  ]]></description>
  
  <change-notes><![CDATA[
    <b>Version 1.1.1</b>
    <ul>
      <li>Multiple inspections at the same place in the document are now ordered by severity.</li>
      <li>Improved performance of processing inspections which do not contain HTML.</li>
    </ul>
    <b>Version 1.1.0</b>
    <ul>
      <li>Fixed showing inspections that include HTML in their description. (<a href="https://github.com/chylex/IntelliJ-Inspection-Lens/pull/3">PR #3</a> by <a href="https://github.com/KostkaBrukowa">KostkaBrukowa</a>)</li>
      <li>Fixed exception when asynchronous inspections run on a non-EDT thread.</li>
    </ul>
    <b>Version 1.0.0</b>
    <ul>
      <li>Initial version with support for IntelliJ 2022.2 and newer.</li>
    </ul>
  ]]></change-notes>
  
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
  
  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <applicationService serviceImplementation="com.chylex.intellij.inspectionlens.InspectionLensPluginDisposableService" />
  </extensions>
  
  <applicationListeners>
    <listener class="com.chylex.intellij.inspectionlens.InspectionLensPluginListener" topic="com.intellij.ide.plugins.DynamicPluginListener" />
  </applicationListeners>
  
  <projectListeners>
    <listener class="com.chylex.intellij.inspectionlens.InspectionLensFileOpenedListener" topic="com.intellij.openapi.fileEditor.FileOpenedSyncListener" />
  </projectListeners>
</idea-plugin>
